[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：您可以通过检索获得一个节点。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: You can get a node by retrieving.
我更喜欢的方式是get document.getElementById。
The way I prefer to do it is get document.getElementById.
您还可以通过名称、标记名称来获取内容。
You can also get things by name, by tag name.
你可以做CSS查询和类似的事情。
You can do CSS queries and things like that.
现在有很多方法可以访问节点。
There's quite a lot of ways of getting access to a node now.
一旦您拥有对节点的访问权限，就可以对其进行操作。
Once you have access to a node, you can manipulate it.
这些是图像标签的标准属性。
So these are the standard properties of an image tag.
如果您有权访问图像标签，则可以更改这些属性中的任何一个。
And if you have access to an image tag, you can change any of these properties.
要更改的最有趣的是源代码，如果您将源代码替换为
The most interesting one to change is the source if you replace the source with
不同的URL。
a different URL.
然后突然会出现一张不同的图片。
Then suddenly a different picture will show up.
JavaScript提供了一种非常方便的方法。
And JavaScript provides a very convenient way of doing that.
您只需说node.property name等于您希望它具有的任何值，并且
You just say node.property name equals whatever value you want it to have and
它起作用了。
it works.
这些是图像标记的标准属性。
These are the standard properties of an image tag.
每个浏览器都将具有独特的附加属性
Every browser will have additional properties that are unique
到那个浏览器。
to that browser.
我建议你远离那些东西，因为这是个陷阱。
I recommend stay away from that stuff because it's a trap.
如果你想留在共同的部分，所以你会在任何地方工作。
If you wanna stay to the common part, so you'll work everywhere.
W3C对JavaScript不满意，
W3C was not happy about JavaScript,
在他们拒绝后在网络上生存。
surviving in the web after they'd rejected it.
他们以为这就是结局，但事实并非如此
They thought that was gonna be the end of it but it didn't and
在W3C中，对Java的同情比对JavaScript的同情要多得多。
there was a lot more sympathy for Java at W3C than for JavaScript.
所以多年来他们一直在努力
And so over the years they've been trying to
将API替换为对Java更友好的东西
replace the API with something that would be more friendly for Java than for
JavaScript，尽管Java从未以这种方式存在于浏览器中。
JavaScript even though Java has never lived in browsers in this way.
所以他们不喜欢老式的做事方式。
So they didn't like the old school way of doing things.
所以他们增加了这个，我们可以调用获取贡品并设置贡品。
So they added this one, we can call get tribute and set tribute.
这种形式有明显的优势，那就是更多的打字和
This form having the obvious advantage, that's a lot more typing and
像那样的人。
people like that.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：获得节点后可以做的另一件事是
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Another thing you can do when you've got hold of a node is
设计它。
style it.
所以你有很多造型选择。
So you've got lots of options for styling.
一个是你可以得到它的类名，这是一个命名错误的东西。
One is you can get at its class name, which is a misnamed thing.
它应该是.class，但它不是，
it should be .class but it's not,
它被称为类名，即使它可以是几个类名。
it's called class name even though it can be several class names.
它仍然是班名。
It's still class name.
更有趣的是，您可以获得样式对象并更改样式的属性。
More interesting as you can get at style object and change attributes of the style.
微软增加了一个非常好的东西，叫做currentStyle，但是
Microsoft added a really nice thing called currentStyle but
有时，您想知道某项内容的当前属性是什么。
sometimes you want to know what is the current attribute for something.
我想知道某样东西有多大，或者它在哪里，或者它现在是什么颜色。
I want to know how big something is or where it is or what color it is currently.
差不多吧。
Something like that.
微软提供了一种很好的方法来找出这一点。
And Microsoft provides a very nice way of finding that out.
但是W3C说，不，这不是我们想要的方式。
But W3C said, no that's not the way we wanna go.
相反，我们更希望您编写document.defaultview.getComputed样式
Instead we'd rather have you write document.defaultview.getcomputed style
节点获取属性值样式名称，对。
node get property values style name, right.
这显然是一个Java API，对吧。
This is obviously a Java API, right.
我的意思是知道JavaScript的人都不会写这个。
I mean nobody who knows JavaScript would write that.
这显然是由一个对JavaScript一无所知的人设计的。
This is clearly designed by somebody who did not know anything about JavaScript.
我不知道Java世界里他们想写的人会发生什么
And I don't know what happens with people in the Java world that they wanna write
像这样的东西，但事情就是这样发生的。
stuff like this but that's kind of the way things happen.
所以我需要咆哮一会儿。
So I need to rant for a moment.
因此CSS和DOM几乎都是在同一时间设计的。
So the CSS and the DOM were both designed about the same time.
每个项目都意识到了另一个。
And each project was aware of the other.
设计CSS的人知道有一天编程语言会
The guy who designed CSS was aware that some day programming languages were going
操纵样式表，这不是必然的。
to manipulate style sheets, not that was a certainty.
但他选择使用减号作为连字符，
And yet he chose to use the minus sign as a hyphen,
知道我们的大多数编程语言都想用它做减法
knowing that most of our programming languages want to do subtraction with it
这给你们所有人造成了句法上的困难。
and that this creates a syntactic difficulty for all of you.
不管怎么说，是他做的。
He did that, anyway.
同时，在Netscape，他们正在研究DOM和
Meanwhile, at Netscape they're working on the DOM and
他们看到CSS刚刚发生了什么，他们就走了。
they see what just happened to CSS and they go.
好吧，那我们该怎么办？
Okay, what are we gonna do about that?
他们可能会说，嗯，这很烦人，但是
What they could have said was, well, that's annoying but
我们只是说你拿着括号，然后把绳子放进去，就这样，所以。
we'll just say you take the brackets and you put the string in, that's that, so.
你必须键入额外的字符，但它是完全兼容的。
You have to type for extra characters but it was completely compatible.
或者他们可能会说，减号是个问题，所以
Or they could have said, well minus signs are a problem, so
我们只是把它们换成酒吧。
we'll just change them to under bars.
所以最小的改变，搜索和替换配置，没有。
So minimal change, search and replace config, no.
他们用最不相容的方式写这些名字。
They went with the least compatible way of writing these names.
&GT；&GT；Douglas Crockford：这很重要，
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: And it matters,
因为你需要知道我现在哪个空间？
cuz you need to be aware of which space am I in right now?
我是在CSS空间，还是在DOM空间？
Am I in CSS space, or am I in DOM space?
这真的很容易让人感到困惑，你在哪里，
And it's really easy to get confused about where you are and
如果你选择了错误的表格，那就完全失败了。
if you pick the wrong form, it's total failure.
他们本可以使这项工作成为一个系统。
They could have made this work like a system.
他们本可以为你做好这件事，但他们选择不这样做
They could have made this work well for you and they chose not to and
它还在那里，永远也修不好了。
it's still there and it's never gonna get fixed.
无论如何，你可以用节点做的另一件事是你可以做节点。
Anyway, so another thing you can do with nodes is you can make nodes.
您可以创建全新的节点。
You can make brand new nodes.
所以你可以调用document.createElement，传入一个标记名，比如DIV或
So you can call document.createElement, pass in a tag name like a DIV or
一些东西，你就会得到一个新的元素。
something and you get a new element.
这个新元素还看不见，而且
That new element is not visible yet and
它将不可见，直到您将其粘贴到树中。
it won't be visible until you paste it into the tree.
我们下一步就这么做。
We'll do that next.
您可以相同的方式创建文本节点。
You can make text nodes the same way.
您传递一个字符串来创建文本节点，它将使您成为一个文本节点。
You pass a string to create text node and it will make you a text node.
然后您可以将其附加到其他节点。
Which you can then attach to some other node.
另一种创建节点的方法是通过克隆已有的节点。
Another way you can make nodes is by cloning nodes that you already have.
克隆人并不是完美的副本。
A clone is not a perfect copy.
例如，节点上可能有事件处理程序，但是
For example a node might have event handlers on it, but
克隆节点不会。
a cloned node will not.
但在其他方面都很相似。
But otherwise it's pretty similar.
如果将true传递给cloneNode，
And if you pass true to cloneNode,
然后，如果节点有子节点，您也将获得子节点的克隆。
then if the node has children, you'll get clones of the children as well.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：所以如果你想让它可见，
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So if you wanna make it visible,
你必须把它插在树上。
you have to stick it into the tree.
因此，您可以调用一个节点并说appendChild，即新节点。
So you can call a node and say appendChild, the new node.
因此新节点成为该节点的新的最后一个子节点。
And so the new node becomes the new last child of that node.
你也可以在前面插入东西
And you can also insert things before and
可以用不同的节点替换节点。
you can replace a node with a different node.
同样，这是一个Java API。
And again, this is a Java API.
因为你必须说两遍老的。
Because you have to say old twice.
就像我可以说的，节点，用这个代替你自己。
Like I could just say, node, replace yourself with this.
不，您必须告诉节点父节点替换该子节点
No, you have to tell the nodes parent replace that child
有了这个方法，找到父节点就是节点本身。
with that one in the way find the parent is with the node itself.
你为什么要写两遍旧的？
Why do you have to write old twice?
为什么Java人要这样做？
Why did Java people do that?
无论如何，你必须移除孩子。
Anyway, you have to remove children.
因此可以调用node.removeChild，但同样不会告诉节点删除
And so you can call node.removeChild but again you don't tell the node to remove
它本身，你必须告诉父母移动它，所以你必须做两次。
itself, you have to tell the parents to move it, so you have to do it twice.
这里有一个特别的危险
There's a particular hazard here for
垃圾收集，如果您使用的是较旧的IE浏览器之一。
garbage collection, if you're on one of the older IE browsers.
那么，有人支持IE6，7，8吗？
So, anybody supporting IE6, 7, 8?
你伤透了我的心。
You're breaking my heart.
真的吗？
Really?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：遗产，是的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Legacy, and it's, yeah.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：好的，那么
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Okay, so
我本来希望我不用再说这些了，但我真的说了。
I was hoping I wouldn't have to say this anymore but I do.
因此IE中存在设计错误。
So there is a design error in IE.
如果您将事件处理程序附加到节点，
That if you attach a event handler to a node,
该节点不会被垃圾收集。
that node will not get garbage collected.
并且事件处理程序和它所持有的所有内容都不会得到垃圾
And the event handler and everything that it's holding onto will not get garbage
即使从树中删除该节点也会收集。
collected even if you remove that node from the tree.
因此，要求您必须删除中的所有事件处理程序
So, the requirement is that you have to remove all of the event handlers from
从树中删除节点之前的节点。
the node before you remove the node from the tree.
这对任何人来说都太过分了，但这就是你必须要做的。
Which is too much to ask of anybody but that's what you have to do.
它在IE6中被识别，它应该在IE7中被修复，但它没有。
It was identified in IE6, it was supposed to be fixed in IE7, and it wasn't.
它本来应该在IE8中修复的，但它没有。
It was supposed to be fixed in IE8 and it wasn't.
我相信它最终在IE9中得到了修复。
I believe it finally did get fixed in IE9.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：所以有时候你想要做的就是获取一个HTML片段
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So sometimes what you want to do is take a fragment of HTML
文本并以某种方式将其合并到文档中。
text and incorporate that into the document somehow.
和W3C在他们的API中没有提供很好的方法来做到这一点。
And W3C in their API provided no good way to do that.
他们的模型是，您将用JavaScript编写XML解析器。
Their model was, you would write an XML parser in JavaScript.
并让它解析文本，然后您将
And have it parse the text, and then you would
调用我刚才展示的所有方法，并让它构建结构。
call all the methods that I just showed you and have it build the structure.
微软说，不，那是太多的工作了，所以他们想出了一个属性
Microsoft said, no that's way too much work, so they came up with a property
一个名为innerHTML的节点的名称，这是一个可怕的名称。
of a node called innerHTML, which is a terrible name.
但它起作用了。
But it works.
因此，您要做的就是为其分配一个HTML文本片段，然后它将对其进行解析
So, what you do is your assign an HTML text fragment to that and it will parse it
然后把它变成一棵树并把它粘贴到文档中，做所有这些，非常好。
and turn it into a tree and stick it into the document, do all of that, very nice.
不幸的是，这是一个安全隐患。
Unfortunately, it's a security hazard.
任何时候您都可以对HTML文本进行任何操作，特别是通过连接，但是
Any time you have any manipulation of HTML text, particularly by concatenation but
同样，通过模板，攻击者很有可能利用这一点。
also by templating, there is a good chance that an attacker can exploit that.
所以你需要非常谨慎地对待这些东西。
So you need to be really, really cautious with this stuff.
那么哪种方式更好呢？
So which way is better?
构建或克隆元素并将其附加到文档中是更好的做法还是
Is it better to build or clone elements and append them to the document or
用HTML文本编译并使用HTML实现更好吗？
is it better to compile in HTML text and using HTML to realize it.
一般来说，我想回答的这些问题就是，
Generally, these sorts of questions I want to answer in terms of,
是什么让你的代码更干净，维护更好？
what gives you a cleaner code and better maintenance?
现在，什么最符合你制作应用程序的方式
Now, what best matches the way you make the application
你应该只在真正重要的情况下才倾向于表现？
that you should only favor performance in cases where it really matters?
在真正重要的情况下，您希望在我们的HTML中使用。
In the cases where it really matters, you wanna use in our HTML.
浏览器真正擅长的几件事之一就是解析HTML。
It's one of the few things that browsers are really good at is parsing HTML.
而且他们可以很快地做到这一点
And they can do that really quickly and
他们可以在一次交易中完成整个事情。
they can get the whole thing done in one transaction.
而摆弄DOM，
Whereas messing with the DOM,
每次你碰DOM你都要付一大笔罚金。
every time you touch the DOM you're gonna pay a big time penalty.